I see that look upon your face
Something my mind cannot erase
If we keep staring
Then I might have to
Might have to start to walk your way
I wanna hear what you would say
You got high standards
And I do too
Cause all those girls
(They don’t)
Know what you need
But I know I know
The way the way
To make to make sure you never leave
If I come close baby would you like that
If I give some would you give it right back
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
Say you want love boy I know what that means
Make you feel way better than in your dreams
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
Yo it’s like that like that
How you run it right back
know you on the right track
Queen ace blackjack
I be thinking way too much
I need to let it go
You be running through my mind
And I’mma let it show
Cause ain’t nobody stepping up to me
And saying nothing when I calling you
Be running eye to eye we never fronting yeah
We zoning bet we stunting on and on and on and
On and on and on and on
To the top baby boy we be rolling
Cause all those girls
(They don’t)
Know what you need
But I know I know
The way the way
To make to make sure you never leave
If I come close baby would you like that
If I give some would you give it right back
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
Say you want love boy I know what that means
Make you feel way better than in your dreams
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
I want you
In my arms
My arms
That’s where you need to be
In my arms
My arms
That’s where you need to be
Ah ah ah ah
But I know I know
The way the way
To make to make sure you never leave
If I come close baby would you like that
If I give some would you give it right back
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
Say you want love boy I know what that means
Make you feel way better than in your dreams
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
If I come close baby would you like that
If I give some would you give it right back
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that
Say you want love boy I know what that means
Make you feel way better than in your dreams
If I show you that I know where it’s at
Baby would you like that